In this fast-paced world, people are often burdened with a
variety of financial and emotional worries.
This
fast-paced lifestyle
makes them vulnerable to major medical events,
often referred to as critical illnesses. Such
illnesses and accidents can have a negative impact
on your bank balance. Such
events, such as unfortunate death or
death, or even hospitalization,
can impact a person's ability to meet their financial obligations, such as
repaying loans or meeting daily expenses.
To meet the needs of such customers, choose ICICI Roba's Criti
Sha Plus, a plan that ensures
that protection does not stop. It helps you during
any major or minor illness covered under the policy,
major surgery, or if you meet with
an accident.
ICICI Roba's
Criti Sha Plus comes with several key benefits,
such as coverage for critical illnesses in floods,
coverage for 106 surgical procedures, cancer rehabilitation benefit, and
multiple payouts for critical illnesses. This plan
covers major and minor critical illnesses in the plan. It is based on a critical illness plan.  The
payout is
100% for major critical illnesses and
25% for minor critical illnesses
categorized into: Cancer and blood
disorders, Heart and blood vessels, Major organs,
Nervous system, Other diseases. The best part is
that there is no waiting period between claims.
And that's not all. Cut-off Plus
also offers optional coverage for 106 surgical procedures, depending on the severity. The
payout is 100% for major surgeries and
50% for minor surgeries. The plan
also offers a cancer benefit.
You will be eligible to claim under this benefit
if you renew the policy,
subject to receiving the premium for the cancer and blood disorders bucket and cancer benefit as per the basic sum insured at the time of renewal. When illnesses are on the rise, it's
better to stay protected. The
Multiple Pay for Critical Illness option
allows you to claim from each of the five critical illness buckets, both major and minor. Don't wait for a
life-threatening or critical illness to strike and [ __ ] you;
plan for it today.  Protect yourself and
your family
With ICICI Lobar's Kashi Plus, not only will you be
covered for a major emergency,
but you can also rely on
quick and easy in-house claim
processing and 24/7 support from our experts.
In this fast-paced world, people are often
burdened with various financial and emotional worries. Besides, they
lead a hectic lifestyle. This makes them
prone to major medical events,
often called critical illnesses.
Such illnesses and accidents can have a negative
impact on your bank account. Such
events can lead to unfortunate
death or disability.